{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/1338","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1338","name":"Columbo's Coney Island","address":"5414 Vernor St.W.","zipcode":"48209","owner":"Hyseni Besnik","licenseNumber":"035471","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-83.10111,42.31832","geojson":{"id":"1338","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.101107219,42.318323385]},"properties":{"name":"Columbo's Coney Island","owner":"Hyseni Besnik","address":"5414 Vernor St.W.","zipcode":"48209","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"035471","establishmentid":"1338","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":"2022-05-05"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51624051","name":"Nepantla Food Trailer, LLC ","address":"5410 W. Vernor Hwy","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"1452","name":"El Palenque","address":"5426 Vernor St. W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"204","name":"Ruiz's Drop In","address":"5442 Vernor W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"259","name":"Duly's Coney Island","address":"5458 Vernor St. W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"51623071","name":"La Fiesta Ice Cream & Luncheria","address":"4824 Vernor W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"2707","name":"New York Pizza & Subs","address":"5620 Vernor W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"954","name":"Covenant House/Life Skills","address":"5668 BAKER ST","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"4677","name":"La Fiesta Ice Cream Shop","address":"4801 W. Vernor Hwy","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"4311","name":"Holy Redeemer Church","address":"1721 Junction","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"4312","name":"Holy Redeemer Church","address":"1721  Junction Ave.","zipcode":"48209"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"60109","inspectionDate":"2022-08-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"GRILL AREA","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-08-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-502.11","violationDescription":"(A) UTENSILS shall be maintained in a state of repair or condition that complies with the requirements specified under Parts 4-1 and 4-2 or shall be discarded.\n(B) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be calibrated in accordance with manufacturer's specifications as necessary to ensure their accuracy. (Pf)   \n(C) Ambient air temperature, water pressure, and water TEMPERATURE MEAURING DEVICES shall be maintained in good repair and be accurate within the intended range of use.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not calibrated","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Dishwasher (high temperature)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-08-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"gnats","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"Without use of trapping devices","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"PESTS","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-08-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Utilize trapping devices to help eliminate pests."},{"violationCode":"5-203.13","violationDescription":"At least 1 service sink or 1 curbed cleaning facility equipped with a floor drain shall be provided and conveniently located for the cleaning of mops or similar wet floor cleaning tools and for the disposal of mop water and similar liquid waste.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Mop/utility sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"Mop sink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2022-08-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"Stove","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"Cooler (3 door)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room(s)","subItem":"employee","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Self-closing door","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"Door","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide self-closing door."}]},{"inspectionid":"57022","inspectionDate":"2022-01-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Ice machine","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-02-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-302.11","violationDescription":"A supply of toilet tissue shall be available at each toilet.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Toilet paper","subItem":"at toilet in restroom men's","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"Toilet paper","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-01-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"5-203.13","violationDescription":"At least 1 service sink or 1 curbed cleaning facility equipped with a floor drain shall be provided and conveniently located for the cleaning of mops or similar wet floor cleaning tools and for the disposal of mop water and similar liquid waste.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Mop/utility sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"Mop sink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-904.14","violationDescription":"After being cleaned and SANITIZED, EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS shall not be rinsed before air drying or use unless:    \n(A) The rinse is applied directly from a potable water supply by a warewashing machine that is maintained and operated as specified under Subparts 4-204 and 4-501; and   \n(B) The rinse is applied only after the EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS have been SANITIZED by the application of hot water or by the application of a chemical SANITIZER solution whose EPA-registered label use instructions call for rinsing off the SANITIZER after it is applied in a commercial WAREWASHING machine.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"Three Compartment sink set-up","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"intake air ducts","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"SEATING AREA","subLocation":"Ceiling vent cover(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"7-209.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, EMPLOYEES shall properly store their PERSONAL CARE ITEMS.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Personal items","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Personal items","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Relocate."}]},{"inspectionid":"56435","inspectionDate":"2021-10-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"restroom","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-11-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hot water."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"gnats","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"Without use of trapping devices","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"PESTS","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-11-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Utilize trapping devices to help eliminate pests."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Freezer (upright)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"55177","inspectionDate":"2021-06-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Prep cooler","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-06-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"violationCode":"4-501.112","violationDescription":"In a mechanical operation, the temperature of the fresh hot water SANITIZING rinse as it enters the manifold may not be more than 194 F, or less than 165 F for stationary rack machines or 180 F for all other machines to assure proper sanitizing of utensils. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Dish machine final rinse temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than 165 degrees F","subProblem":"For hot water sanitizing machine For single rack, single temperature","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"SANITIZING","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-06-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"Hand-drying towels","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-06-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"5-203.13","violationDescription":"At least 1 service sink or 1 curbed cleaning facility equipped with a floor drain shall be provided and conveniently located for the cleaning of mops or similar wet floor cleaning tools and for the disposal of mop water and similar liquid waste.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Mop/utility sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"Mop sink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"53601","inspectionDate":"2020-12-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-502.11","violationDescription":"(A) UTENSILS shall be maintained in a state of repair or condition that complies with the requirements specified under Parts 4-1 and 4-2 or shall be discarded.\n(B) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be calibrated in accordance with manufacturer's specifications as necessary to ensure their accuracy. (Pf)   \n(C) Ambient air temperature, water pressure, and water TEMPERATURE MEAURING DEVICES shall be maintained in good repair and be accurate within the intended range of use.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Air/water thermometer(s)","subItem":"cooler reach in","problemDescription":"Not accurate","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"Cooler (2 door)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Replace."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Cooler (2 door)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"5-203.13","violationDescription":"At least 1 service sink or 1 curbed cleaning facility equipped with a floor drain shall be provided and conveniently located for the cleaning of mops or similar wet floor cleaning tools and for the disposal of mop water and similar liquid waste.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Mop/utility sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"Mop sink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"cabinets","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Prep cooler","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"52502","inspectionDate":"2020-08-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"51727","inspectionDate":"2020-04-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"51063","inspectionDate":"2020-03-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"restroom womens","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hot water."}]},{"inspectionid":"49918","inspectionDate":"2019-11-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-11-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-501.112","violationDescription":"In a mechanical operation, the temperature of the fresh hot water SANITIZING rinse as it enters the manifold may not be more than 194 F, or less than 165 F for stationary rack machines or 180 F for all other machines to assure proper sanitizing of utensils. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Dish machine final rinse temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than 165 degrees F","subProblem":"For hot water sanitizing machine For single rack, single temperature","location":"BAR(HIGH TOP)","subLocation":"Dishwasher","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."},{"violationCode":"5-203.13","violationDescription":"At least 1 service sink or 1 curbed cleaning facility equipped with a floor drain shall be provided and conveniently located for the cleaning of mops or similar wet floor cleaning tools and for the disposal of mop water and similar liquid waste.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Mop/utility sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"Mop sink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"Plumbing","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Equipment","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room(s)","subItem":"employee","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Self-closing door","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"Self-closing device","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-12-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide self-closing door."},{"violationCode":"4-904.11","violationDescription":"(A) SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES and cleaned and SANITIZED UTENSILS shall be handled, displayed, and dispensed so that contamination of FOOD- and lip-contact surfaces is prevented.   \n(B) Knives, forks, and spoons that are not prewrapped shall be presented so that only the handles are touched by EMPLOYEES and by CONSUMERS if CONSUMER self-service is provided.   \n(C) Except as specified under ¶ (B) of this section, SINGLE-SERVICE ARTICLES that are intended for FOOD- or lip-contact shall be furnished for CONSUMER self-service with the original individual wrapper intact or from an APPROVED dispenser.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Utensil(s)","subItem":"single-service","problemDescription":"Stored with food-contact portion exposed","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Single service items","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-12-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store inverted."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Floor","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-12-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Equipment","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-12-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."}]},{"inspectionid":"48749","inspectionDate":"2019-08-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Ice machine","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"2-103.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall ensure that employees, practices and policies are in compliance with the code. (Pf) \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not ensuring compliance","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Glove usage","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Person-in-charge must ensure compliance with items listed above."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Floor","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"47657","inspectionDate":"2019-05-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"RAW FOOD STORAGE","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-05-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"SANITIZING","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-05-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Equipment/utensils must be sanitized after cleaning."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"ACCESS","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-05-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Make easily accessible."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"ceiling(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Ceiling tile(s)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-05-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"VENTILATION HOOD SYSTEM","subLocation":"Ventilation hood filters","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Certified Manager","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-05-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"Light intensity","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-05-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"45962","inspectionDate":"2019-04-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"44139","inspectionDate":"2018-11-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.112","violationDescription":"In a mechanical operation, the temperature of the fresh hot water SANITIZING rinse as it enters the manifold may not be more than 194 F, or less than 165 F for stationary rack machines or 180 F for all other machines to assure proper sanitizing of utensils. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Dish machine final rinse temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than 165 degrees F","subProblem":"For hot water sanitizing machine For single rack, single temperature","location":"BAR(HIGH TOP)","subLocation":"Front counter","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-04-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Meat slicer","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-02-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"DINING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"violationCode":"6-202.112","violationDescription":"Living or sleeping quarters located on the PREMISES of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT such as those provided for lodging registration clerks or resident managers shall be separated from rooms and areas used for FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations by complete partitioning and solid self-closing doors.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Living/sleeping quarters","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Inadequately separated from retail establishment","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide approved complete and adequate separation between living/sleeping quarters and retail establishment."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored in soiled, wet conditions","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN (FRONT AREA)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-11-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store in protected manner."},{"violationCode":"2-401.11","violationDescription":"(A)    An EMPLOYEE shall eat, drink, or use any form of tobacco only in designated areas where the contamination of exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES; or other items needing protection can not result.\n(B)     A FOOD EMPLOYEE may drink from a closed BEVERAGE container if the container is handled to prevent contamination of:\n         (1)     The EMPLOYEE'S hands;\n         (2)     The container; and\n         (3)     Exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Smoking","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Smoke only in designated areas as restricted above."}]},{"inspectionid":"42697","inspectionDate":"2018-06-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"42093","inspectionDate":"2018-04-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-04-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Hands shall be washed with hot water and soap for at least 20 seconds after contamination."},{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-04-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-04-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Handwashing sinks are to be accessible for use at all times"},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"Surfaces of Ice bin","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"40086","inspectionDate":"2017-09-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-303.11","violationDescription":"After use as a medium for cooling the exterior surfaces of FOOD, or cooling coils and tubes of EQUIPMENT, ice may not be used as FOOD. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ice","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used as a cooling medium","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"Surfaces of Ice bin","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Cannot be used for food"},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"Surfaces of Ice bin","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Establishment shall provide a clear date marking system."},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"Surfaces of Ice bin","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Surfaces of Ice bin","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"38426","inspectionDate":"2017-03-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cloths that are in use for wiping FOOD spills on TABLEWARE shall be maintained dry and used for no other purpose. \n(B)  Cloths in-use for wiping counters and equipment shall be held between uses in   a chemical sanitizer solution, and laundered daily.\n(C)  Cloths in-use for wiping surfaces in contact with raw animal FOODS shall be      kept separate from cloths used for other purposes.\n(D)  Dry wiping cloths and the chemical sanitizing solutions shall be free of FOOD    debris or visible soil.\n(E)  Containers of chemical sanitizing solutions shall be stored off the floor and         used in a manner that prevents contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, SINGLE-SERVICE, or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n(E)  SINGLE-USE disposable sanitizer wipes shall be used in accordance lable               instructions.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"37064","inspectionDate":"2016-10-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-10-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1338"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}